And send Me the children ….
把孩子送來…
Now come along, wash My Feet.
現在來吧，為我清洗雙腳
Come along, both of you, come along.
來吧，你們兩個，來吧
Now put up your sleeves first of all,
先捲起衣袖
put up your sleeves properly. Good.
好好捲起衣袖
Both the hands.
用雙手
Salutations to the one who incarnates as the past.
(瑜伽士︰向過往降世神祇禮拜
Bhuta bhava.
Bhuta bhava)
All the left side. He’s at the base of the left side,
全在左邊，他是左邊的根基
so you’ll understand what is he telling.
所以你會明白他在說甚麽
He’s the left side, the past.
他是左邊，過去
“Bhuta” is “past.”
“Bhuta”是過去
No, ... you first say the meaning.
不…你先說它的意思
Then you say this, so they will understand;
接著你說這個，那麽他們便會明白
it goes into the head, all right? The first is the meaning.
它走到頭，對嗎？先是意思
Now, second one you say.
現在，你說第二個
“Bhuta sangha” means the collection of all that is created.
“Bhuta sangha” 是指「全部被創造的」
“Bhuta sanghana videha manah”:
“Bhuta sanghana videha manah”:
“videha” means “ in the body”,
“videha”是指「在身體裡」
“manah” means “in the heart of that body,” in Sanskrit.
“manah”是指「在這個身體的心裡」，梵文
… In the heart.
在心中
“Bhutatmanaha”. Atmana is the Spirit.
“Bhutatmanaha”. Atmana 是「靈」
“Bhut” means “created”: whatever is created,
“Bhut” 指「創造」；無論創造甚麽
He resides them as the Spirit.
他以靈住在他們裡
“Bhutatmanaha.”
“Bhutatmanaha.”
Now here I would like to say that it is Shri Ganesha
現在在這裡，我要說這是格涅沙
who is the Omkara, who is the vibrations.
祂是 Omkara，祂是生命能量
So He is the truth. What He says is the truth,
所以祂是真理，祂說的是真理
so, what vibrations say is the truth.
生命能量說的都是真理
He's truth.
祂是真理
So Omkara is vibrations, that is Shri Ganesh.
所以 Omkara 是生命能量，這就是格涅沙
“Paramadhama”.
“Paramadhama”.
Too much. Too much.
太多了，太多了
Better take one with ….
最好與這個一起拿著…
Now, you have to tie up those ….
現在，你要繫好它…(印地語)
Let them take photograph.
讓他們拍照
Now, can you come?
現在你能來嗎？
Be careful.
小心點
Can you tie?
你能繫好它嗎？
Did you avoid in the photograph these things? Did you avoid?
你在照片中能避開這東西嗎？你能避開嗎？
...showing?
展示？
No, no, take it out, that one.
不，不，拿它出來，這一個
It’s a good photograph, all right?
這是張好照片，對嗎？
So that it’s a formidable photograph.
這是幀傑出的照片
with the head of Shri Ganesha.
有格涅沙的頭
May God bless you all.
願神祝福你們
Oh God...Wow, beautiful. Thank you.
噢！天呀，哇，很漂亮，謝謝
From the italian sahaja yogis.
來自意大利的霎哈嘉瑜伽士
It is too much for Me. Thank you very much.
對我太多了，很感謝你們
What is that?
這是甚麽？
Wow, beautiful! Very nice. From where did you get it?
哇，很漂亮。他們從哪裡取得它？
Oh, I see, is very good.
噢，我明白，是很好的
What is this? She's come from Austria all the way?
這是甚麽？她來自澳地利？
… Ah! From Austria! Thank you very much ….
…呀！來自澳地利！很感謝…
Thank you very much. How beautiful it is. Very beautiful.
很感謝，它很漂亮，很漂亮
Thank you very much.
非常感謝